{
    "id": "0dea06b7815947f9871cbbf982bd8665",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Nothing about the accident ……………….. to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knew",
                "was known",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "810b6dd617ef4cbeaac61b6bccc61a43"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. the thief …………………. by the police?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Has, caught",
                "Has, been caught",
                "Was, been caught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1cbb4f40e2d04c768c2512eed6b4caaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "My feelings ………………….. by his caustic remarks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have hurt",
                "hurt",
                "were hurt"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bc5a39ac6ad14cc5b59bd32cf21f0b66"
        },
        {
            "question": "An order …………………. by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has placed",
                "has been placed",
                "placed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f9876029eeb4631b5240ee997812f74"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody ………………….. by her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was betrayed",
                "has been betrayed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ab222a78e8324033ac50c78f659bb4a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The animals ………………….. by the poachers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hunted",
                "were hunting",
                "were being hunted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db3857a1729e447e865c78407712193f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Prizes ………………….. away by the chief guest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are giving",
                "were being gave",
                "were being given"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2942bb6882e2499689529ea1bc77cc25"
        },
        {
            "question": "His life ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must have saved",
                "must save",
                "must be saved"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b81cce92ad5342dbab803eb32e31f984"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… by grief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has overwhelmed",
                "was overwhelmed",
                "was overwhelming"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "518f743de96a44bfa74b559e29fa2efd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient ………………….. medicine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is administering",
                "is being administered",
                "has administered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "753c5b3344a2435cb1b886d495dc167c"
        }
    ]
}